[ WOMAN SCREAMING ]
[ OMINOUS HOWLING ]
[ OMINOUS LAUGHTER ]
[ DOOR CREAKING AND OPENING ]
[ WIND CHIME CHIMING ]
[ DOOR CREAKING AND CLOSING ]
[ OMINOUS HOWLING ]
THE GHOSTS ARE MOVING TONIGHT , RESTLESS , HUNGRY .
MAY I INTRODUCE MYSELF ?
I 'M WATSON PRITCHARD .
IN JUST A MINUTE I 'LL SHOW YOU
THE ONLY REALLY HAUNTED HOUSE IN THE WORLD .
SINCE IT WAS BUILT A CENTURY AGO
SEVEN PEOPLE , INCLUDING MY BROTHER ,
HAVE BEEN MURDERED IN IT .
SINCE THEN , I 'VE OWNED THE HOUSE .
I 'VE ONLY SPENT ONE NIGHT THERE
AND WHEN THEY FOUND ME IN THE MORNING
I WAS ALMOST DEAD .
I 'M FREDERICK LOREN .
AND I 'VE RENTED THE HOUSE ON HAUNTED HILL TONIGHT ,
SO THAT MY WIFE CAN GIVE A PARTY .
A HAUNTED HOUSE PARTY .
SHE 'S SO AMUSING .
THERE 'LL BE FOOD AND DRINK AND GHOSTS .
AND PERHAPS EVEN A FEW MURDERS .
YOU 'RE ALL INVITED .
IF ANY OF YOU WILL SPEND THE NEXT 12 HOURS IN THIS HOUSE ,
I 'LL GIVE YOU EACH $ 10,000
OR YOUR NEXT OF KIN , IN CASE YOU DON 'T SURVIVE .
AH , BUT HERE COME OUR OTHER GUESTS .
LOREN : IT WAS MY WIFE 'S IDEA
TO HAVE OUR GUESTS COME IN FUNERAL CARS .
[ LAUGHS ] SHE 'S SO AMUSING .
HER SENSE OF HUMOR IS , SHALL WE SAY , ORIGINAL .
I DREAMED UP THE HEARSE . IT 'S EMPTY NOW ,
BUT AFTER A NIGHT IN THE HOUSE ON HAUNTED HILL ,
WHO KNOWS .
THIS IS LANCE SCHROEDER , A TEST PILOT ,
SO , NO DOUBT A BRAVE MAN .
BUT DON 'T YOU THINK YOU CAN BE MUCH BRAVER
IF YOU 'RE PAID FOR IT ?
AND I HAPPEN TO KNOW THAT LANCE NEEDS THE 10,000
I 'LL GIVE HIM
IF HE 'S BRAVE ENOUGH TO STAY ALL NIGHT .
THIS IS RUTH BRIDGERS .
YOU 'VE NO DOUBT READ HER COLUMN IN THE NEWSPAPERS .
SHE SAYS HER REASON FOR COMING TO THE PARTY
IS TO WRITE A FEATURE ARTICLE ON GHOSTS .
SHE 'S ALSO DESPERATE FOR MONEY , GAMBLES .
YOU 'VE ALREADY MET WATSON PRITCHARD ,
A MAN LIVING IN MORTAL FEAR OF A HOUSE
AND YET HE IS RISKING HIS LIFE
TO SPEND ANOTHER NIGHT HERE . I WONDER WHY ?
HE SAYS FOR MONEY .
THIS IS DR. DAVID TRENT , A PSYCHIATRIST .
HE CLAIMS THAT MY GHOSTS WILL HELP HIS WORK ON HYSTERIA ,
BUT DON 'T YOU SEE A LITTLE TOUCH OF GREED THERE ,
AROUND THE MOUTH AND EYES ?
THIS IS NORA MANNING .
I PICKED HER FROM THE THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE WHO WORK FOR ME ,
BECAUSE SHE NEEDED THE 10,000 MORE THAN MOST .
SUPPORTS HER WHOLE FAMILY .
ISN 'T SHE PRETTY ?
THE PARTY 'S STARTING NOW , AND YOU HAVE UNTIL MIDNIGHT
TO FIND THE HOUSE ON HAUNTED HILL .
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
WELL , WHERE IS EVERYBODY ?
IT ISN 'T A VERY WARM WELCOME , IS IT ?
ONLY THE GHOSTS IN THIS HOUSE ARE GLAD WE 'RE HERE .
ARE WE ALL STRANGERS TO EACH OTHER ?
DON 'T YOU TWO KNOW EACH OTHER ?
I 'M AFRAID I DON 'T EVEN KNOW YOUR NAME .
I 'M NORA MANNING .
LANCE SCHROEDER .
IS FREDERICK LOREN A FRIEND OF YOURS ?
I 'VE HEARD OF HIM , BUT I 'VE NEVER MET HIM .
I WORK FOR ONE OF HIS COMPANIES ,
BUT I 'VE NEVER SEEN HIM .
I 'VE NEVER MET THE MAN EITHER .
JUST A PHONE CALL . DO YOU KNOW HIM ?
NO .
BRIDGERS : WELL , THEN YOU 'RE THE ONLY ONE OF US WHO DOES .
I DON 'T KNOW HIM .
ALL THE DETAILS ABOUT RENTING THE HOUSE
WERE DONE BY MAIL .
HE 'S QUITE WEALTHY , ISN 'T HE ?
MILLIONS .
AND FIVE WIVES , I BELIEVE .
FOUR , I THINK SO FAR .
A $ 50,000 PARTY FOR ONLY FIVE PEOPLE
IS A LITTLE STEEP ,
EVEN FOR A MILLIONAIRE .
[ CHUCKLES ]
WELL , IF I WERE GONNA HAUNT ANYBODY ,
THIS WOULD CERTAINLY BE THE HOUSE I 'D DO IT IN .
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
[ GLASS JINGLING ]
WHO CLOSED THE DOOR ?
THIS THING IS MADE OF SOLID STEEL .
ANNABELLE ?
OUR GUESTS ARE HERE AND FORTUNATELY STILL ALIVE .
IS YOUR FACE ON YET ?
DUST AND DIRT EVERYWHERE AND THE WATER BARELY TRICKLED .
COULDN 'T YOU HAVE HAD THE PLACE CLEANED ?
ATMOSPHERE , DARLING .
YOU KNOW HOW GHOSTS ARE , THEY NEVER TIDY UP .
THAT 'S A VERY FETCHING OUTFIT ,
BUT HARDLY SUITABLE FOR A PARTY .
I 'M NOT GOING TO THE PARTY .
THIS SPEND-THE-NIGHT GHOST PARTY WAS YOUR IDEA , REMEMBER ?
SINCE IT 'S GONNA COST ME $ 50,000 ,
I WANT YOU TO HAVE FUN .
THE PARTY WAS MY IDEA ,
UNTIL YOU INVITED ALL THE GUESTS .
WHY ALL THESE STRANGERS , WHY NONE OF OUR FRIENDS ?
FRIENDS ? DO WE HAVE ANY FRIENDS ?
NO , YOUR JEALOUSY TOOK CARE OF THAT .
I HAD A REASON FOR INVITING EACH GUEST .
I WANTED KIND OF A CROSS-SECTION .
FROM PSYCHIATRIST TO TYPIST ,
AND FROM DRUNK TO JET PILOT .
THEY SHARE ONE THING : THEY ALL NEED MONEY .
NOW , LET 'S SEE IF THEY 'RE BRAVE ENOUGH TO EARN IT .
AND YOU CALL THIS A PARTY ?
COULD BE .
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS DO THAT ? IT SPOILS THE CHAMPAGNE .
IT MIGHT EXPLODE .
NEVER DOES .
WOULD YOU GUARANTEE THAT ?
THAT ISN 'T FUNNY , FREDERICK .
IT WOULD MAKE A GOOD HEADLINE :
" PLAYBOY KILLS WIFE WITH CHAMPAGNE CORK . "
WILL YOU JOIN ME ?
NO , THANK YOU .
JUST A SIP MIGHT IMPROVE YOUR HUMOR .
MY HUMOR IS FINE , THANKS .
AND I HAVEN 'T POISONED IT .
IT 'S ALWAYS GOOD TO KNOW THAT .
HAVE SOME .
YOU 'LL ENJOY THE PARTY MORE .
GO ON .
YOUR TRUST IS SO TOUCHING .
AND I 'M NOT GOING TO THE PARTY .
OF ALL MY WIVES YOU ARE THE LEAST AGREEABLE .
BUT STILL ALIVE .
[ CHUCKLES ]
WOULD YOU GO AWAY FOR A MILLION DOLLARS , AND TAX FREE ?
YOU WANT IT ALL , DON 'T YOU ?
I DESERVE IT ALL .
YOUR JEALOUSY ISN 'T TAX FREE .
AND YOUR POSSESSIVENESS IS MADDENING .
IF EVER A MAN HAD GROUNDS FOR DIVORCE ...
BUT CAN 'T PROVE THEM .
THE TIME WILL COME .
YOU 'LL SLIP UP ONE OF THESE DAYS .
THINK SO ?
IF I LIVE LONG ENOUGH .
YOU REMEMBER THE FUN WE HAD WHEN YOU POISONED ME ?
SOMETHING YOU ATE , THE DOCTOR SAID .
YES , ARSENIC ON THE ROCKS .
ANNABELLE ... YOU 'D DO IT AGAIN
IF YOU THOUGHT YOU COULD GET AWAY WITH IT , WOULDN 'T YOU ?
DARLING , WHAT MAKES YOU THINK THAT ?
SOMETHING ABOUT YOU .
I HEAR THAT HANGING IS VERY UNCOMFORTABLE ,
IN CASE YOU GET ANY MORE IDEAS .
AND DON 'T LET THE GHOSTS AND THE GHOULS
DISTURB YOU , DARLING .
DARLING , THE ONLY GHOUL IN THE HOUSE IS YOU .
AND DON 'T SIT UP ALL NIGHT
THINKING OF WAYS TO GET RID OF ME .
IT MAKES WRINKLES .
THIS IS WHAT SHE USED ON MY BROTHER AND HER SISTER .
HACKED ' EM TO PIECES .
WE FOUND PARTS OF THE BODIES ALL OVER THE HOUSE .
IN PLACES YOU WOULDN 'T THINK .
A FUNNY THING IS , THE HEADS HAVE NEVER BEEN FOUND .
HANDS AND FEET AND THINGS LIKE THAT ,
BUT NO HEADS .
THE WIFE , PROBABLY IN A RAGE ,
THREATENED HER HUSBAND WITH THE KNIFE
AND THEN , CARRIED AWAY BY HYSTERIA ,
TOOK A SWING AT HIM AND SIMPLY WENT ON FROM THERE .
SHE CERTAINLY WENT ON .
HOW MANY PEOPLE DID SHE KILL , MR. PRITCHARD ?
ONLY TWO .
HER HUSBAND AND HER SISTER . NO ONE ELSE WAS HERE .
SO THERE ARE TWO LOOSE HEADS JUST FLOATING AROUND
IN HERE SOMEWHERE ?
YOU CAN HEAR THEM AT NIGHT .
THEY WHISPER TO EACH OTHER AND THEN CRY .
[ LAUGHS ]
SINCE OUR HOST ISN 'T HERE ,
WOULD ANYONE CARE TO MIX ME A DRINK ?
CERTAINLY . WHAT WILL YOU HAVE ?
[ DOOR OPENING ]
GOOD EVENING .
I AM YOUR HOST , FREDERICK LOREN .
SINCE WE 'RE ALL STRANGERS TO EACH OTHER ,
LET 'S GET ACQUAINTED WITH A DRINK , SHALL WE ?
MR. LOREN ...
I ADVISE YOU TO CALL THIS PARTY OFF NOW .
THE GHOSTS ARE ALREADY MOVING AND THAT 'S A BAD SIGN .
LET ME APOLOGIZE FOR MY WIFE , SHE 'LL JOIN US LATER .
WHAT WILL YOU HAVE ?
SCOTCH AND ...
DOCTOR ?
I 'LL HAVE THE SAME .
NOW , BEFORE THE PARTY BEGINS ,
LET 'S GO OVER THE DETAILS .
THE CARETAKERS WILL LEAVE AT MIDNIGHT ,
LOCKING US IN HERE UNTIL THEY COME BACK IN THE MORNING .
ONCE THE DOOR IS LOCKED , THERE IS NO WAY OUT .
THE WINDOWS HAVE BARS THAT A JAIL WOULD BE PROUD OF
AND THE ONLY DOOR TO THE OUTSIDE LOCKS LIKE A VAULT .
THERE IS NO ELECTRICITY , NO PHONE ,
NO ONE WITHIN MILES ,
SO , NO WAY TO CALL FOR HELP .
LIKE YOUR COFFIN .
SO , IF ANY OF YOU DECIDE NOT TO STAY FOR THE PARTY
YOU MUST LET ME KNOW BEFORE MIDNIGHT .
OF COURSE , IF YOU LEAVE ,
I SHAN 'T BE ABLE TO PAY YOU ANYTHING .
I 'M INTERESTED IN YOUR REASONS FOR THIS ...
PARTY .
ASIDE FROM THE PLEASANT COMPANY .
GHOSTS , DOCTOR .
I THINK EVERYONE WONDERS WHAT THEY WOULD DO
IF THEY SAW A GHOST .
AND NOW MY WIFE IS GIVING US ALL THE OPPORTUNITY TO FIND OUT .
[ CHUCKLES ] AMUSING .
GHOSTS , ETCETERA ,
BEING ONLY CREATIONS OF HYSTERIA ,
YOUR PARTY SHOULD BE A SUCCESS .
BUT PRITCHARD HERE PROMISES US GENUINE GHOSTS .
SEVEN NOW .
AND MAYBE MORE BEFORE MORNING .
THAT 'S CHEERFUL .
FOUR MEN HAVE BEEN MURDERED IN THIS HOUSE .
AND THREE WOMEN .
YOU PLANNED YOUR PARTY VERY WELL , MR. LOREN .
FOUR OF US ARE MEN , THREE ARE WOMEN .
A GHOST FOR EVERYBODY .
THEN PRITCHARD , WHY DON 'T YOU TAKE US ON A TOUR
THROUGH THE HOUSE AND LET 'S SEE WHAT HAPPENS , HUH ?
PRITCHARD : SEE THAT STAIN ?
BLOOD .
A YOUNG GIRL WAS KILLED HERE .
AND WHATEVER GOT HER , WASN 'T HUMAN .
DON 'T STAND THERE !
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ? WHERE ?
IT 'S TOO LATE , THEY 'VE MARKED YOU .
RIDICULOUS , THE ROOF PROBABLY LEAKS .
THAT MUST BE WHAT IT IS . WHO WOULD WANNA HAUNT ME ?
I WOULD SAY ANY SELF-RESPECTING MALE GHOST .
I HOPE IT DOESN 'T COME BACK .
WELL , MR. PRITCHARD , YOU 'RE THE LIFE OF THE PARTY .
HE HASN 'T EVEN STARTED YET .
WASN 'T THERE A MAN WHO THREW HIS WIFE IN A WINE VAT OR SOMETHING ?
THAT WAS IN THE CELLAR .
THERE 'S BEEN A MURDER ALMOST EVERY PLACE IN THIS HOUSE .
ALL THIS BELONGED TO A MR. NORTON
WHO DIDN 'T DIE HERE , HE WAS ELECTROCUTED LATER .
MR. NORTON DID A GOOD DEAL EXPERIMENTING WITH WINES ,
BUT HIS WIFE DIDN 'T THINK IT WAS ANY GOOD .
SO , HE FILLED A VAT WITH ACID
AND THREW HER IN .
SHE WAS SUPPOSED TO STAY DOWN ,
BUT THE BONES CAME UP .
IT 'S A FUNNY THING ,
BUT NONE OF THE MURDERS HERE WERE JUST ORDINARY .
JUST SHOOTING OR STABBING ,
THEY 'VE ALL BEEN SORT OF WILD ,
VIOLENT AND DIFFERENT .
LOOK OUT !
THANK GOD SHE DIDN 'T FALL IN .
YOU MEAN THERE 'S STILL ACID IN THERE ?
DESTROYS EVERYTHING WITH HAIR AND FLESH .
JUST LEAVES THE BONES .
MY , IT 'S DRY AND DUSTY DOWN HERE .
WELL , THERE 'S A CURE FOR THAT UPSTAIRS . COME ON .
HOW DID YOU GET INVITED TO THIS PARTY ?
NO . LET THEM GO ON .
I MEAN , WHAT DID HE TELL YOU ?
[ SIGHS ] MR. LAUREN SAID
EVERYBODY WOULD GET $ 10,000 .
BUT HE DIDN 'T SAY ANYTHING ABOUT BEING LOCKED IN .
NO .
HE JUST MADE A DEAL WITH ME ON THE PHONE ,
BUT NOTHING ABOUT HAVING TO STAY .
AREN 'T YOU GONNA STAY ?
IF I DON 'T , I LOSE $ 10,000 .
I 'M GONNA STAY , TOO .
$ 10,000 .
YEAH .
DO YOU BELIEVE IN GHOSTS ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
WELL , I AGREE WITH WHAT THAT DOC SAYS .
YOU CAN SPOOK YOURSELF .
I 'VE DONE IT IN PLANES .
I 'VE SEEN THINGS THAT WEREN 'T REALLY THERE .
OR WERE THEY ?
WHAT 'LL YOU DO WITH YOUR 10,000 ?
IF WE GET IT .
WHAT DO YOU MEAN IF WE GET IT ?
WON 'T HE PAY US IF WE STAY ?
AH , SURE HE WILL .
10,000 IS NO MORE TO HIM THAN A NICKEL IS TO US .
WE WERE IN AN AUTOMOBILE ACCIDENT .
NOW I 'M THE ONLY ONE IN THE FAMILY WHO CAN MAKE ANY MONEY .
BOY , I 'VE NEVER SEEN SO MANY DOORS .
CLOSET .
BOTTLES .
DOES IT GO ANYWHERE ?
LANCE !
HELP ME , PLEASE !
LANCE IS GONE AND THERE 'S A GHOST .
A GHOST ?
PLEASE , PLEASE , COME ON !
DID SHE SAY LANCE IS GONE ?
GONE WHERE ?
WE 'LL HAVE TO BREAK IT DOWN , IT 'S LOCKED .
LOCKED ?
YOU ALL RIGHT ?
NOTHING THAT MONEY WON 'T CURE .
I MUST HAVE BUMPED MY HEAD .
AND THE ONLY WAY YOU COULD BUMP YOUR HEAD IN HERE
IS TO RUN HEAD ON INTO THE WALL .
YOU DIDN 'T DO THAT , DID YOU ?
LET 'S GET A BANDAGE ON THAT .
I WONDER WHY THEY DIDN 'T KILL HIM .
WHO ?
HE DIDN 'T BUMP HIS HEAD .
THEY HIT HIM .
THEY ?
NORA ...
WHEN YOU CAME IN , YOU SAID SOMETHING ABOUT A GHOST .
THERE WAS SOMETHING .
WHAT DID IT LOOK LIKE ?
WELL , IT WAS WEARING A BLACK THING
THAT WENT ALL THE WAY TO THE FLOOR .
WEREN 'T YOU A LITTLE FRIGHTENED AT THE TIME ?
WELL , YES .
THAT , MR. LOREN , IS HYSTERIA .
BUT THEN DOCTOR , HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN
WHAT HAPPENED TO LANCE ?
WAS THAT HYSTERIA TOO ?
YOU BETTER GET THAT CHECKED IN A DAY OR SO .
THANKS , DOC .
WAIT FOR ME IN THE HALL .
THE GHOSTS ARE COMING CLOSER , MR. LOREN .
YOU REALLY BELIEVE IN YOUR PET GHOST ,
DON 'T YOU , PRITCHARD ?
BEFORE THE NIGHT 'S OVER , YOU WILL TOO .
WOULDN 'T YOU LIKE A DRINK , LANCE ?
NO , THANKS .
I 'D LIKE ONE . SCOTCH AND ...
MR. LOREN , ARE YOU REALLY GOING TO PAY ANYONE
WHO STAYS ALL NIGHT ?
CERTAINLY . $ 10,000 .
WILL THERE BE MUCH RED TAPE ? DELAY ?
YOU IN A HURRY , DEAR ?
FRANKLY , YES .
OR FRANTICALLY .
THERE YOU ARE , MY DEAR .
[ CLOCK TICKING ]
SOMEONE OR SOMETHING WAS IN HERE WHEN I CAME IN .
BUT WHERE ?
AND IF THE DOOR WAS LOCKED , HOW DID IT GET OUT ?
WHAT YOU SAW , MIGHT HAVE BEEN A GHOST , NORA ,
BUT WHAT WAS IN HERE WITH ME WAS NO GHOST .
I DON 'T KNOW , I WAS SO SCARED .
DOES THAT SOUND DIFFERENT TO YOU ?
YES .
THREE , SIX , NINE , TWELVE .
TWELVE FEET .
THREE , SIX .
NOW I 'M GONNA KNOCK ON THE OTHER WALL .
WHEN YOU HEAR ME , YOU KNOCK ON THIS WALL .
[ KNOCKING ]
LANCE : TAP LOWER DOWN .
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SOBBING ]
OH , LANCE !
I SAW IT AGAIN !
WHERE DID IT COME FROM ?
FROM IN HERE .
WELL , IF IT RAN OUT OF HERE , I 'D HAVE SEEN IT .
LANCE , IT DOESN 'T RUN , IT JUST FLOATS .
YEAH , BUT WHY DIDN 'T I SEE IT ?
YOU DON 'T BELIEVE ME .
WELL , HOW CAN I ?
I 'M ANNABELLE LOREN .
YOU MUST BE MISS MANNING .
I REALIZE THIS IS A VERY UNUSUAL
AND I 'M AFRAID VERY DULL PARTY .
WOULDN 'T YOU LIKE TO FRESHEN UP ?
THIS IS YOUR ROOM .
DEPRESSING , ISN 'T IT ?
I DOUBT IF I 'LL SPEND MUCH TIME HERE .
IT 'S GOING TO RAIN .
PERFECT ATMOSPHERE FOR MY HUSBAND 'S PARTY .
WHY DID YOU COME HERE ?
HE SAID HE 'D GIVE ME $ 10,000 .
WHY DID HE PICK YOU ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
MY SUPERVISOR JUST CAME AND SAID I 'D BEEN INVITED .
HOW LONG HAVE YOU KNOWN MY HUSBAND ?
I JUST MET HIM TONIGHT .
SO ?
WHY YOU ?
WHAT WERE YOU DOING WANDERING AROUND BY YOURSELF ?
WELL , I WAS IN THE CELLAR WITH LANCE ... MR. SCHROEDER ,
I JUST LEFT , THAT 'S ALL .
DON 'T DO IT AGAIN .
DON 'T GO ANYWHERE IN THIS HOUSE BY YOURSELF .
NOW , FIX YOUR FACE
AND I 'LL COME BACK FOR YOU IN A FEW MINUTES .
BUT I ...
YOU 'RE IN DANGER .
WE ALL ARE .
BUT WHO ?
I HOPE FOR YOUR SAKE YOU NEVER FIND OUT .
I 'M ANNABELLE LOREN , WERE YOU LOOKING FOR SOMETHING ?
NOT EXACTLY .
ARE YOU THE DOCTOR ?
NO . NO , I 'M LANCE SCHROEDER .
THE PILOT . YOU 'VE HURT YOURSELF .
OH , IT 'S JUST A BUMP ON THE HEAD .
WHICH IS MY ROOM ?
I BELIEVE THIS IS IT .
THANK YOU , MRS. LOREN .
ANNABELLE , LANCE .
YOU WERE WITH THE YOUNG GIRL IN THE CELLAR .
WHY WAS SHE SO UPSET ?
WAS SHE ?
AND YOU DON 'T LOOK LIKE THE TYPE TO GO AROUND BUMPING HIS HEAD .
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED , LANCE ?
WELL , NORA THOUGHT SHE SAW A GHOST ,
BUT I DIDN 'T SEE ANYTHING .
SHE WAS JUST FRIGHTENED THEN ?
AND MAD AT ME , I THINK . I KIDDED HER ABOUT IT .
I WOULDN 'T JOKE ABOUT ANYTHING ELSE THAT HAPPENS HERE TONIGHT .
NOW , DON 'T TELL ME YOU ARE TAKING ALL THIS SERIOUSLY ?
AREN 'T YOU ?
WELL , I 'D LIKE TO FIND OUT WHAT HIT ME .
LANCE ...
IF I NEED HELP , MAY I COUNT ON YOU ?
YEAH . SURE , I GUESS SO .
LOOK , WHAT 'S GOING ON HERE ANYWAY ?
I MEAN , WHAT IS WITH THIS PARTY BIT ?
THIS IS NO PARTY , HE 'S PLANNING SOMETHING .
YOUR HUSBAND ?
I WISH I KNEW WHAT IT WAS .
MUST BE PRETTY BIG , IF HE 'S GONNA LAY OUT 50,000 .
MONEY DOESN 'T MEAN ANYTHING .
HE HAS A REASON FOR GETTING US ALL UP HERE
TO THIS DREADFUL OLD HOUSE .
WHAT FOR ? HE DOESN 'T EVEN KNOW US .
MAYBE THAT 'S EXACTLY WHY YOU 'RE HERE .
WELL , WHAT CAN HE GET AWAY WITH ?
OH , HE THINKS THAT BIG MONEY LIKE HIS
CAN GET AWAY WITH ANYTHING .
YOU KNOW , OF COURSE , THAT I 'M HIS FOURTH WIFE .
THE FIRST SIMPLY DISAPPEARED ,
THE OTHER TWO DIED .
LANCE ...
I DON 'T WANNA JOIN THEM .
YOU MEAN HE ...
OH , HIS DOCTORS SAID THEY DIED OF HEART ATTACKS .
TWO GIRLS , IN THEIR TWENTIES .
WELL , WHAT CAN HE DO ?
MY HUSBAND IS SOMETIMES INSANE WITH JEALOUSY ,
NOTHING MATTERS TO HIM THEN .
PLEASE , BE CAREFUL .
WOULD HE HURT YOU ?
HE WOULD KILL ME IF HE COULD .
ANNABELLE , YOU 'RE MISSING ALL THE FUN .
NORA MANNING WAS ALMOST KILLED BY A FALLING CHANDELIER ,
THE PILOT BASHED HIS HEAD IN .
IS HE BADLY HURT ?
THE SATURNINE PSYCHIATRIST BANDAGED HIM UP .
DON 'T YOU WANT TO GO AND CONSOLE HIM ?
AS YOU DO MOST MEN IN YOUR FASHION ?
YOU 'RE SO CLEVER , FREDERICK .
AS I LIE AWAKE NIGHTS WONDERING WHY I MARRIED YOU .
IT WAS RATHER A MISTAKE .
YOU DIDN 'T MARRY ME , DEAR , I MARRIED YOU .
UNPLEASANT , BUT NO MISTAKE .
WELL , HURRY UP .
FREDERICK , FOR THE LAST TIME , I 'M NOT GOING TO YOUR PARTY .
AND FOR THE LAST TIME , IT 'S NOT MY PARTY , BUT YOURS .
AND YOU ARE GOING .
I AM NOT .
YOU READY , DEAR ?
NO .
ARE YOU READY , DEAR ?
YES . DAMN YOU !
WOULD YOU ADORE ME AS MUCH IF I WERE POOR ?
ALL YOU WANNA BE IS A LOVELY WIDOW .
IT 'S ALMOST TIME TO LOCK UP THE HOUSE .
AND THEN YOUR PARTY WILL REALLY BEGIN .
I WONDER HOW IT 'LL END .
IT 'S CLOSE TO MIDNIGHT , LANCE .
OK , I 'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE .
NORA : WHO IS IT ?
YOUR HOST , MY DEAR .
IT 'S ALMOST MIDNIGHT , NORA .
WE 'RE ALL GOING TO GET TOGETHER DOWN IN THE LIVING ROOM .
ALL RIGHT , MR. LOREN . I 'LL BE RIGHT DOWN .
[ GRUNTING ]
COME WITH US .
COME WITH US BEFORE HE KILLS YOU .
[ SCREAMING ]
[ CLOCK TICKING ]
WHERE 'S NORA ? MISS MANNING ?
I DON 'T WANNA STAY HERE !
NORA , WHAT HAPPENED ?
[ DOORS CREAKING ]
THAT 'S JONAS SLYDES AND HIS WIFE .
THEY 'VE BEEN CARETAKERS HERE FOR YEARS .
SHE 'S BLIND , YOU KNOW .
I 'M NOT GOING TO STAY HERE !
WELL , DOCTOR , IT LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE
A REAL CASE OF HYSTERIA ON OUR HANDS .
I THINK SHE 'S JUST A LITTLE UPSET ,
NOT HYSTERICAL .
[ DOOR OPENING ]
GOOD EVENING .
HELLO , MY DEAR .
THIS IS MY WIFE . THESE ARE OUR GUESTS .
RUTH BRIDGERS , DR. TRENT ,
YOU KNOW WATSON PRITCHARD , OF COURSE , NORA MANNING ,
AND THIS IS LANCE SCHROEDER .
GET ME OUT OF HERE .
WHAT ABOUT THE 10,000 ?
I DON 'T CARE , HE WANTS TO KILL ME .
WHO WANTS TO KILL YOU ?
MR. LOREN .
[ CLOCK TICKING ]
FREDERICK : MAY I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION , PLEASE ?
I THINK YOU ALL REMEMBER THE BARGAIN WE MADE
ABOUT STAYING ALL NIGHT .
$ 10,000 A PIECE .
IF ANY OF YOU DON 'T SURVIVE ,
$ 50,000 WILL BE DIVIDED AMONGST THE REST OF YOU .
IF I SHOULD DIE ...
YOU WILL BE PAID BY MY ESTATE .
WHEN THE DOOR IS LOCKED FROM THE OUTSIDE BY THE CARETAKERS ,
WE 'LL ALL BE FORCED TO STAY IN THIS HOUSE UNTIL MORNING .
IF ANY OF YOU DECIDE NOT TO STAY ,
YOU MUST LEAVE WITH THE CARETAKERS NOW .
YOU WON 'T HAVE A CHANCE TO CHANGE YOUR MINDS LATER ,
BECAUSE THERE 'LL BE NO WAY TO GET OUT .
I DON 'T WANNA STAY !
WAIT .
[ WIND BLOWING ]
[ DOOR SLAMMING SHUT ]
IT ISN 'T MIDNIGHT YET .
WHO TOLD THEM THEY COULD LEAVE ?
THEY NEVER LEAVE BEFORE MIDNIGHT .
WELL , THEY 'VE GONE NOW .
I WAS GOING TO ASK YOU WHETHER YOU WANTED TO STAY OR NOT ,
BUT IT SEEMS THAT THE CARETAKERS HAVE MADE THE DECISION FOR YOU .
WE 'RE ALL LOCKED IN NOW .
BUT I DON 'T WANNA STAY .
I 'M SORRY , MY DEAR , BUT IT 'S TOO LATE NOW .
DARLING , HAVEN 'T YOU HAD ENOUGH OF THIS SILLY GAME ?
GET SOME CARS UP HERE FOR THESE PEOPLE AND LET THEM GO HOME .
BUT PAY THEM FIRST .
THIS IS YOUR PARTY , REMEMBER ?
IN SPITE OF MY WIFE 'S FAITH IN MY ABILITY
TO DO THE IMPOSSIBLE ,
WE WILL ALL HAVE TO STAY IN THIS HOUSE
UNTIL EIGHT O 'CLOCK IN THE MORNING .
BUT WE HAVE SOME PARTY FAVORS FOR YOU
IN THESE LITTLE COFFINS .
THIS IS MY WIFE 'S IDEA .
AND I MUST SAY , I THINK IT 'S RATHER DANGEROUS .
I SUPPOSE YOU ALL KNOW HOW TO USE ONE OF THESE THINGS ,
BUT IN CASE YOU DON 'T ,
YOU JUST PRESS DOWN ON THIS LEVER WITH YOUR THUMB .
AND THEN PULL THE TRIGGER .
YOU SEE , THEY 'RE LOADED .
THESE ARE NO GOOD AGAINST THE DEAD , ONLY THE LIVING .
DOCTOR .
LANCE .
NORA .
GO AHEAD . TAKE IT .
MISS BRIDGERS .
AND HERE 'S YOURS , DEAR .
I DON 'T NEED IT .
IT WAS YOUR IDEA .
WHO KNOWS , YOU MAY WANT TO USE IT ON ME
BEFORE THIS NIGHT IS OVER .
THROW THESE GUNS AWAY . THEY WON 'T DO YOU ANY GOOD .
I AGREE WITH PRITCHARD ON THAT POINT ,
ALTHOUGH NOT FOR THE SAME REASON .
DR. TRENT ...
DON 'T YOU APPROVE OF OUR LITTLE PARTY FAVORS ?
SUPPOSE NORA HAD HAD A GUN
WHEN SHE MISTOOK THE BLIND WOMAN FOR A GHOST .
I DON 'T THINK ANYONE ELSE
IS GOING TO WALK AROUND IN TOTAL DARKNESS .
OH , I 'M SURE WE 'RE NOT GONNA GO RUNNING AROUND THE HOUSE
SHOOTING EACH OTHER , AREN 'T YOU ?
WHO KNOWS ?
FEAR MAKES PEOPLE DO AMAZING THINGS .
MR. PRITCHARD ...
YOU SAID YOUR SISTER-IN-LAW KILLED A MAN AND A WOMAN HERE
AND CUT THEM UP ?
YOU SAID THEY FOUND HANDS AND FEET ,
BUT THEY NEVER FOUND ANY HEADS .
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE ONE OF THOSE HEADS ?
WOULD YOU ALL LIKE TO SEE ONE OF THOSE HEADS ?
WELL , THEN ... JUST FOLLOW ME .
DARLING ...
I REALLY DON 'T NEED THIS .
JUST GO LOOK IN MY SUITCASE . JUST GO LOOK .
BUT IT WAS IN THERE . A WOMAN 'S HEAD !
NORA , I THINK YOU 'RE A LITTLE UPSET .
WOULD YOU CARE FOR A SEDATIVE ?
GET OUT ! GET OUT , ALL OF YOU !
ALL OF YOU GET OUT OF HERE AND LEAVE ME ALONE !
JUST GET OUT OF HERE !
DO YOU THINK IT 'S ALL RIGHT TO LEAVE HER BY HERSELF , DOCTOR ?
I WISH SHE 'D TAKEN A SEDATIVE .
WHAT DO YOU SUPPOSE SHE THOUGHT SHE SAW ?
THEY 'RE CLOSING IN ON HER .
LOOK , DOC , I THINK SOMEBODY OUGHT TO STAY WITH HER .
THERE COULD BE A MILLION PEOPLE AROUND HER .
AND IF THEY WANTED HER , THEY 'D GET HER .
WHAT IF HE 'S RIGHT ?
HE 'S TOO DRUNK TO KNOW WHAT HE 'S TALKING ABOUT .
I WONDER .
I 'LL JOIN YOU IN A MINUTE .
DO YOU THINK IT WOULD DO ANY GOOD IF YOU WENT IN AND ...
TALKED TO HER ?
DO YOU THINK THERE REALLY WAS A HEAD IN HER SUITCASE ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
A THING LIKE THAT WOULD PUT ME RIGHT OVER THE EDGE .
LOOK , WOULD YOU SORT OF STAY UP HERE
I MEAN , IN CASE SHE NEEDS HELP ?
ALL RIGHT . I 'LL BE IN MY ROOM .
JUST CALL IF YOU NEED ME .
THANKS .
ARE YOU SURE THERE ARE ONLY SEVEN PEOPLE IN THIS HOUSE ?
POSITIVE . EXCEPT FOR THE GHOSTS .
I DON 'T BELIEVE IN GHOSTS .
NOR IN FRIGHTENING WOMEN .
IN NORA 'S CASE IT 'S GONE FAR ENOUGH .
PERHAPS TOO FAR .
WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST WE DO ABOUT IT , DOCTOR ?
DON 'T FRIGHTEN HER ANYMORE .
NORA .
NORA ?
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
NORA !
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS ?
THEY 'VE TAKEN HER .
IN A LITTLE WHILE , SHE 'LL BE ONE OF THEM .
WHERE IS NORA ?
WHERE IS SHE ?
IT 'S TOO LATE . IT 'S TOO LATE .
YOU 'LL NEVER FIND HER AGAIN .
PRITCHARD , IF YOU KNOW WHERE SHE IS , YOU BETTER TELL ME NOW !
SHE 'S GONE ! SHE 'S GONE WITH HIM .
AND THERE IS NOTHING YOU CAN DO ABOUT IT .
[ WOMAN SCREAMING ]
[ WOMAN CHOKING ]
NORA .
TAKE HER DOWN .
NORA ?
SHE 'S DEAD , MR. LOREN .
YOUR WIFE HANGED HERSELF .
A SUICIDE .
NORA : LANCE !
NORA !
LANCE , HIDE ME ! PLEASE , HIDE ME !
WHAT 'S THE MATTER ?
HIDE ME !
[ CRYING ] HE TRIED TO KILL ME .
HE GRABBED ME AND CHOKED ME AND PUT ME IN THAT ROOM .
AND THEN HE WENT AWAY AND LEFT ME .
WHO ?
HE THOUGHT I WAS DEAD .
MR. LOREN .
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS ?
I DON 'T KNOW . IT WAS DARK , BUT IT MUST HAVE BEEN HIM .
HAS ANYBODY SEEN YOU SINCE HE LEFT YOU ?
I HEARD SOME PEOPLE IN THAT ROOM ,
BUT I WENT BY AND NOBODY SAW ME .
MRS. LOREN IS DEAD .
BUT HOW ?
LOREN SAID SHE COMMITTED SUICIDE .
BUT I THINK SOMEBODY KILLED HER .
HIM ?
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
I 'M SURE YOU 'VE COME TO THE SAME CONCLUSION I HAVE .
YEAH , I THINK SO .
LET 'S ALL HAVE A MEETING , DISCUSS WHAT TO DO .
THE LIVING ROOM ?
OK , IN A MINUTE .
I 'VE GOT TO GO DOWNSTAIRS .
NOW , YOU LOCK YOURSELF IN HERE
AND DON 'T LET ANYBODY KNOW YOU 'RE HERE .
IF HE THINKS YOU 'RE DEAD , HE WON 'T COME HERE .
AND I 'LL GET BACK AS SOON AS I CAN .
YOU 'LL BE ALL RIGHT .
AND IF YOU HAVE TO ...
YOU USE IT .
SO BEAUTIFUL ,
SO GREEDY ,
SO COLD .
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN HERE ?
WAIT . DON 'T WE ... ?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN COMING IN HERE ?
I DIDN 'T WANT THEM TO TAKE HER AWAY .
YOU 'RE DRUNK .
THEY WILL IF YOU DON 'T WATCH HER .
YOU 'RE DRUNK ! ALL RIGHT , OUT WITH IT , PRITCHARD .
WHY DID YOU COME INTO THIS ROOM ?
I 'M THE ONLY ONE WHO UNDERSTANDS .
UNDERSTANDS WHAT ?
YOUR WIFE ISN 'T THERE ANYMORE .
SHE 'S ALREADY JOINED THEM .
NOW PRITCHARD , I 'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOUR SPOOK-TALK .
GET OUT , YOU SOT , AND DON 'T COME BACK INTO THIS ROOM AGAIN .
WHERE IS WHAT 'S HER NAME ? NORA .
I DIDN 'T DISTURB HER , SINCE I DON 'T THINK THIS CONCERNS HER .
NO , YOU 'RE RIGHT .
DR. TRENT : MR. LOREN ...
ISN 'T THERE SOME WAY WE CAN GET OUT OF THIS HOUSE NOW ?
NO , NONE AT ALL .
WE COULD TRY BREAKING OUT .
THE ONLY DOOR TO THE OUTSIDE IS MADE OF STEEL .
THE BARS ON THE WINDOWS ARE SET IN SOLID STONE .
WE 'VE GOTTA STAY .
I 'M NOT AFRAID OF YOUR GHOSTS PRITCHARD .
BUT I AM AFRAID .
WHEN WE CAME HERE A FEW HOURS AGO ,
THE ONLY THING WE HAD IN COMMON WAS THE $ 10,000 WE 'D GET .
NOW , HOWEVER , WE SHARE SOMETHING ELSE :
THE DEATH OF MRS. LOREN .
SO FAR TONIGHT ,
ONE OF US WAS ALMOST KILLED BY A FALLING CHANDELIER .
ONE OF US WAS MYSTERIOUSLY SLUGGED .
ONE OF US HAS BEEN DRIVEN TO THE BRINK OF ABSOLUTE HYSTERIA .
AND ONE OF US IS DEAD .
WERE THESE ACCIDENTS ?
SUICIDE ?
AND WE MUST STAY HERE FOR SIX MORE HOURS .
SIX HOURS ?
SIX OF US .
TIME ENOUGH .
WHO WILL BE NEXT ?
HOW WILL IT HAPPEN ?
LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION , DOCTOR .
YOU WERE THE FIRST ONE TO SEE MY WIFE THERE .
DID YOU ALSO SEE ANYTHING THAT SHE COULD HAVE CLIMBED UP ON
AND THEN JUMPED ?
NO .
DID ANY OF YOU ?
THERE WAS NOTHING .
HOW THEN DID SHE GET UP THERE , SO HIGH ?
EXACTLY , MR. LOREN . HOW ?
SHE COULDN 'T HAVE PULLED HERSELF UP THERE ,
SHE COULDN 'T HAVE DROPPED FROM THE CEILING .
DO YOU THINK YOUR WIFE KILLED HERSELF ?
NO . SHE WAS MURDERED .
BY ONE OF YOU .
OR YOU , MR. LOREN .
TO DELIBERATELY KILL SOMEONE , YOU MUST HAVE A REASON .
WE WERE ALL STRANGERS TO YOUR WIFE .
ONLY YOU HAD A MOTIVE FOR MURDER .
WHAT HUSBAND HASN 'T AT SOME TIME WANTED TO KILL HIS WIFE ?
WHAT HUSBAND HASN 'T HAD A THOUSAND OPPORTUNITIES
TO DO IT IN SUCH A WAY
SO THAT HE 'D NEVER BE SUSPECTED ?
I 'M NOT SUCH A FOOL AS TO HANG MY WIFE
FROM A CEILING BY A ROPE .
THE FACT REMAINS THAT YOU OR ONE OF US
MURDERED MRS. LOREN .
AND THAT 'S A MATTER FOR THE POLICE .
SO , HOW DO WE GET THE POLICE ?
THAT 'S MY POINT . WE CAN 'T UNTIL MORNING .
WHAT BEGAN AS A SILLY PARTY GIVEN BY AN ECCENTRIC ,
HAS NOW INVOLVED US ALL IN MURDER .
FOR ONCE , PRITCHARD MAY BE RIGHT .
IF ANOTHER MURDER 'S IN THE WORKS , LET 'S STOP IT NOW .
ANOTHER MURDER ?
WHY NOT ?
MAYBE ONE OF US SAW TOO MUCH .
WHY SHOULD EVEN A MILLIONAIRE
WANT TO GIVE EACH OF US $ 10,000
TO SPEND ONE NIGHT IN A GLOOMY OLD HOUSE ?
TO SEE SOME GHOSTS ? HAVE A PARTY ?
NO .
HAVE YOU FINISHED TRYING ME , DOCTOR ?
AND IS THE VERDICT " GUILTY OF MURDER " ?
OH , THIS ISN 'T GETTING US ANYWHERE .
SOMEBODY KILLED MRS. LOREN , WE KNOW THAT .
ONE OF US IS GUILTY AND THE REST OF US ARE INNOCENT , OK .
NOW , WHAT WE HAVE TO DO FOR THE NEXT SIX HOURS
IS PROTECT OURSELVES FROM EACH OTHER .
DO YOU REALLY THINK ...
I DON 'T THINK ANYTHING .
I JUST KNOW THAT I 'M GOING TO MY ROOM .
AND IF ANYBODY COMES IN , I 'LL SHOOT HIM .
OR HER .
AND IF WE ALL STAY IN OUR ROOMS , WE 'LL BE SAFE .
BECAUSE THE INNOCENT WILL HAVE NO REASON TO LEAVE HIS ROOM
AND THE GUILTY WILL ADMIT HIS GUILT IF HE OR SHE DOES .
AND WE ALL HAVE GUNS .
THEN WE 'RE ALL AGREED ?
OH , I WISH THIS NIGHT WERE OVER .
ROOMS ? GUNS ?
I TELL YOU , IT DOESN 'T MAKE ANY DIFFERENCE .
THEY AREN 'T THROUGH WITH US YET .
WHAT 'S THE USE IN SAYING GOOD NIGHT ?
GOOD NIGHT .
GOOD NIGHT , DOCTOR .
LANCE : NORA , IT 'S ME , LANCE .
YOU OK ?
THEY 'VE ALL GONE TO THEIR ROOMS AND LOCKED THEMSELVES IN .
LANCE , I 'VE BEEN THINKING .
IT WAS SO DARK DOWN THERE , MAYBE IT WASN 'T MR. LOREN .
IT WAS HIM ALL RIGHT .
HE TRIED TO KILL YOU , AND HE DID KILL HIS WIFE .
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
HOW CAN YOU BE SO SURE ?
SHE TRIED TO WARN ME , ASKED ME TO HELP HER .
THE DOC THINKS HE 'S GONNA TRY AND KILL ONE OF US .
NOW , THERE MUST BE A WAY OUT OF THIS PLACE
AND I 'M GONNA FIND IT AND GET THE POLICE BEFORE HE DOES .
I 'M GOING WITH YOU .
WELL , IF HE FINDS OUT YOU 'RE ALIVE ...
NO , NORA . YOU 'RE SAFER HERE THAN ANY PLACE ELSE .
NOW , JUST LOCK YOURSELF IN AND KEEP QUIET .
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
IF I FIND A WAY OUT , I 'LL COME BACK AND GET YOU .
NO ! NO !
[ SCREAMING ]
LANCE .
[ ORGAN STARTS PLAYING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
AN ADMISSION OF GUILT , DOCTOR ?
CERTAINLY NOT .
THERE 'S EITHER SOMEBODY ELSE IN THIS HOUSE
OR ONE OF US HAS LEFT HIS ROOM .
DID YOU HEAR ANYTHING ?
ORGAN MUSIC ?
THAT ... AND SOMEONE WALKING .
YOU GOT YOURS ?
READY ?
YOU LOOK DOWNSTAIRS AND I 'LL LOOK UP HERE .
WHY NOT TOGETHER ?
THERE MAY BE ONLY MINUTES , SECONDS LEFT OF SOMEONE 'S LIFE .
WHY WASTE TIME ?
IT 'S ALMOST OVER , DARLING .
EVERY DETAIL WAS PERFECT .
WHAT 'S HAPPENING ?
WE 'VE DONE IT . THE PERFECT CRIME .
BEAUTIFUL .
HAS SHE KILLED HIM ?
NOT YET . BUT SHE WILL .
IS HANGING HARNESS .
WHAT 'S TAKING THAT GIRL SO LONG ? WHAT TIME IS IT ?
AT FIRST I COULDN 'T GET NORA
TO WANT TO PROTECT HERSELF WITH A GUN .
BUT AFTER YOU APPEARED AT THE WINDOW
EVERYTHING BEGAN TO WORK JUST AS WE HAD PLANNED .
YOU WERE WONDERFUL .
JUST THE TOUCH THAT FINALLY
DROVE HER INTO COMPLETE HYSTERIA .
IT 'LL BE WORTH ALL OF OUR PLANNING , DARLING .
WHERE 'S NORA NOW ?
WHAT 'S HAPPENING ?
ON HER WAY TO THE CELLAR .
SO SCARED , SHE 'LL SHOOT THE FIRST THING THAT MOVES .
AND FREDERICK ?
ON HIS WAY TO THE CELLAR , TOO .
DAVID , ARE YOU SURE NONE OF THEM WILL SUSPECT US ?
OF WHAT ?
A HYSTERICAL GIRL ACCIDENTALLY SHOOT SOMEBODY ?
WHO WOULD SUSPECT THAT WE PLANNED IT THAT WAY ?
THAT WE DROVE HER TO IT ?
WHAT ABOUT MY SUICIDE ?
WELL , JUST A GHOST PARTY GAG .
WE 'LL CLAIM IT WAS A DUMMY ,
SINCE I 'M THE ONLY ONE WHO TOUCHED YOU .
AND THE CARETAKERS ?
WELL , THEY HAD NO IDEA WHAT THEY WERE REALLY DOING .
WHAT ABOUT NORA ? SHE 'S NOT STUPID , YOU KNOW .
DARLING , BELIEVE ME ,
EVERYTHING WE 'VE PLANNED IS WORKING PERFECTLY .
NORA IS SURE FREDERICK MURDERED YOU .
SHE THINKS FREDERICK ATTACKED HER IN THE CELLAR , NOT ME .
AND NOW NORA IS ALMOST OUT OF HER MIND WITH FEAR .
THE HEADS , THE MUSIC , YOUR HANGING .
I TELL YOU WHEN FREDERICK WALKS IN THERE , SHE 'LL SHOOT HIM .
IT 'S TAKING TOO LONG .
DAVID , YOU OUGHT TO BE THERE .
WHEN YOU HEAR THE SHOT , COME DOWN TO THE CELLAR .
NORA . NO !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ ACID SPLASHING , BUBBLING ]
DAVID ?
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
[ DOORS CREAKING AND SLAMMING SHUT ]
[ ACID BUBBLING ]
FREDERICK 'S VOICE : AT LAST YOU 'VE GOT IT ALL .
EVERYTHING I HAVE ...
EVEN MY LIFE .
BUT YOU 'RE NOT GOING TO LIVE TO ENJOY IT .
COME WITH ME , MURDERESS . COME WITH ME .
[ SCREAMING ]
GOOD NIGHT , DOCTOR .
GOOD NIGHT , ANNABELLE .
THE CRIME YOU TWO PLANNED , WAS INDEED PERFECT .
ONLY THE VICTIM IS ALIVE AND THE MURDERERS ARE NOT .
IT 'S A PITY YOU DIDN 'T KNOW
WHEN YOU STARTED YOUR GAME OF MURDER ,
THAT I WAS PLAYING TOO .
THERE MUST BE SOME WAY TO GET IN HERE .
OH , IT 'S RIGHT ALONG HERE SOMEWHERE .
[ POUNDING ]
LANCE !
I 'VE SHOT MR. LOREN . HE 'S DOWN IN THE WINE CELLAR .
ALIVE ?
I DON 'T THINK SO .
IT 'S HIM ! HE 'S ALIVE !
YOU DIDN 'T SHOOT ANYONE , MY DEAR .
I LOADED YOUR GUN WITH BLANKS .
I CAN TELL YOU ALL NOW ,
TRENT AND MY WIFE WERE PLANNING TO KILL ME .
THEY FAILED .
TRENT TRIED TO THROW ME IN THE VAT .
MY WIFE STUMBLED AND FELL .
I 'M READY FOR JUSTICE TO DECIDE IF I 'M ...
INNOCENT OR ... GUILTY .
NOW THERE ARE NINE .
THERE 'LL BE MORE , MANY MORE .
[ GLASS JINGLING ]
THEY 'RE COMING FOR ME NOW .
AND THEN THEY 'LL COME FOR YOU .
[ OMINOUS LAUGHTER ]
[ DOOR CREAKING ]